♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
=Spring Over Phoenix Pond=
(Adapted from Qin An'an's
"Spring Over Phoenix Pond")
=Episode 5=
(He was actually serious.)
Young Lady Qi,
do you resist me that much?
I will not help you.
I hope Your Highness
does not regret this.
Your subordinate failed.
Someone got to the account book first
and took it.
Who?
Qi Yuan.
How did she know
we were checking the account book?
Where is she?
Early this morning,
the Qi family
set off for Guanyin Temple.
Prepare a horse.
To Guanyin Temple.
(She actually used
the account book to force my hand.)
Ling.
I'm here.
Look, this is written so well.
- This view beats the manor's.
- This one is great.
This one's nice, too.
Yes, indeed.
You can write one too.
Judging by the time,
Prince Jing should be arriving soon.
Lianqiao,
go to the entrance to greet him.
Yes, Young Lady.
(Blessed with Sons)
(Miaoyin Pavilion)
I didn't expect
Your Highness to arrive so soon.
You jerk!
Why did you force Jin away?
Believe it or not, I'll kill you!
Do you think just because Father
holds a welcome ceremony for you,
you become
the daughter of the Qi family?
Let me tell you,
I am the only son of the Qi family.
I am the next Marquis Yongping.
As long as I'm around,
don't ever dream of joining
the family ancestral record.
Once I inherit the title,
I'll sell you to a brothel
and let you suffer endless torment.
I'll make you regret what you did today.
Why don't I just kill you right now
to eliminate
the threat once and for all?
Let go.
There are people all over outside now.
Are you really going
to commit murder here?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I know
the account book is with you.
However, that account book
is of great consequence.
I advise you to hand it over.
Indeed.
I know this account book is connected
to the relief fund corruption case
Your Highness is investigating.
Now that
the account book is in my hands,
I hope Your Highness
can invite the Eldest Princess for me.
Are you threatening me?
This is a negotiation.
If the Eldest Princess doesn't come,
at worst, I'll just return
to the estate.
After all, no matter
how terrible a life it is,
I've already lived through it.
I'm not afraid of losing it.
But what about Your Highness?
This is powerful evidence
to bring down Prince Qi.
Can you bear to give it up?
Mother told me to go to the main hall
at the hour of the Mao to burn incense.
I'll take my leave now.
Hold on.
I can agree to help you,
but you must give me
the account book first.
Once the welcome ceremony is over,
I will present it to you.
Look over there. It's so beautiful.
They bloomed so wonderfully.
Yes.
How lovely.
Sisters,
I heard that for this blessing assembly,
all the noble ladies
of the royal family will attend.
Yet Prince Jing
is the only royal prince present.
Prince Cheng is a bit strange,
so no one dares to ask him to come.
Right.
Prince Qi, on the other hand,
is gentle and refined,
but he seems to have fallen ill recently
and has been in a coma all this time.
In a coma?
(In my past life, Prince Qi was never
said to have a strange illness.)
Xiang Rong, come.
(Xiang Rong...)
(Xiang Rong, Miss Xiang)
(In my past life,)
(she was the only friend
who disregarded my background)
(and was willing to help me.)
Rest assured,
I will cure your leg.
Xiang Rong, you're here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Young Lady Qi,
Qi Zhao's sister.
Aren't you engaged to Qi Zhao?
Don't mention that engagement.
I have other matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave first.
(Just and Honorable, Grand Main Hall)
Madam,
I've had someone examine
their birth charts.
Zhao and Rong are
a match made in heaven.
(Madam Xiang, Xiang Rong's Grandmother)
Marquise Yongping, you acted fast,
even matching
their birth charts already.
Of course.
We are all hoping
that Rong marries into our family soon.
Madam.
Zhao.
Young Lady,
since we are already here,
let's draw a fortune stick as well.
Come on.
Since I have entered the Qi Residence,
that in itself is the best fortune.
Let's go.
Young Lady,
come on.
Draw one.
Hurry.
Alright.
You aren't going
to interpret the fortune?
Since Your Highness
wants it interpreted so much,
you can play with it yourself.
(Worst Luck)
Say not that the east wind is useless,
for a single spark of fire
glows from the east on its own.
(This fortune text
is exactly the same as before.)
At the end of one's rope,
walking on thin ice.
If this is the will of Heaven,
how can a single spark of fire
stand against
a sky full of wind and snow?
Interesting.
A few days ago, my father mentioned
that joy comes after extreme sorrow.
Though this seems
like the worst fortune,
it conceals a favorable turn.
This is clearly
a sign of great auspiciousness.
(When we met in my past life,)
(the Crown Prince
had already passed away.)
(He was always deeply gloomy.)
(Now that the Crown Prince
is still alive,)
(he indeed seems a bit different.)
One does not lie before the Buddha.
Qi Yuan,
what is your background?
Your martial skills aren't those
of an ordinary peasant woman,
and you know
I'm investigating the account book
as well as the corruption.
Before you came to the Qi family,
did you never leave the village?
You investigated me?
Rest assured, Your Highness,
I will never become your enemy.
As a gift of gratitude for inviting
the Eldest Princess on my behalf,
here is a friendly warning.
Pay attention to
the Crown Prince's medicinal decoction.
Go and check my father's diet
to see if there's anything abnormal.
Investigate in secret.
Do not alert the enemy.
Yes.
♪How I wish to hold
onto this fleeting warmth♪
♪How I wish to live
this life only for you♪
♪When memories sink
and the heart settles♪
♪Forgetting life, death,
parting, and reunion♪
♪How I wish to stay
only in the moment with you♪
♪Anchoring myself by your side♪